A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 5: McLean Planning Committee Files, 1967-2001
  - MPC Newspaper Clippings, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - MPC Zoning Violations, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - MPC Board of Directors, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - MPC Minutes; Englat Building Documents, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - MPC Caucus, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - MPC McLean Plaza Development, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - MPC Maps, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Series 6: Fairfax County Planning Files, 1957-2013
  - Sub-series 6-1: PLUS Plan Files, 1970-2001
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Dranesville Environmental Force, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team A Papers, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team B Papers - Land Use Planning Committee Draft Report: Team B, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team C Papers (Part 1), 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team C Papers (Part 2), 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team D Papers (Note: The original file folder containing this material was labeled "Team D," but the majority of the content is "Team A" documents.), 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Capital Project Requests and Plan Documents, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Markup, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Team A Papers - Hollinswood Subdivision Rezoning, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Environmental Quality Corridors, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - 1976 Updates, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Meetings, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - A Handbook for Creating an Urban Development Information System by Fairfax County, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Discussion of Growth Trends and Planning Issues by Samuel A. Finz, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area Seminar on Legal Aspects of Land Use Planning, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Sewer and Water Studies and Newspaper Clippings (Includes a copy of Metropolitan Washington Examiner, vol. 1, no. 1 (November 1974), 1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Land Use - National Wildlife Federation Site, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Disposal or Interim Use of School Sites, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Residential Housing Density, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Citizen Contact Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Noise Ordinance, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Community Bus Service, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Status Report, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - PLUS Plan General Material and Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - "Transferable Development Rights" Study by Supervisor Audrey Moore, 1974, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Transportation Task Force Meeting, 1974 March 30 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Citizen Attitude Survey, 1974 April (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Tour of Problem Areas, 1974 April (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Working Paper, 1974 April (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - McLean Area Resident Questionnaire, 1974 May (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Joint Workshop, 1974 May 4 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - County-Wide Forum, 1974 June (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Dranesville Upper Potomac PLUS Committee Papers (Includes a hand-drawn map of the Great Falls area), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - PLUS Plan McLean Planning District - Area II Map Errors and Changes, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - PLUS Plan - Centreville District Task Force Committee, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - PLUS Plan - Vienna Citizens Task Force, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - PLUS Plan - Jefferson District Task Force, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - PLUS Plan - Pohick District Task Force, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - PLUS Plan - Countywide Plan Changes, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - PLUS Plan - Correspondence RE: John E. Harrison's Criticisms of Plan, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - PLUS Plan - R. W. Cabell Study: "Local Government Budgets, 1950-1969.", 1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - PLUS Plan - R. W. Cabell Study: "The Dranesville Task Force: An Action Program.", 1972 October (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - PLUS Plan - Environmental Quality Advisory Council, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - PLUS Plan - Bullsneck Run Trail, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - PLUS Plan - Site Plan Notices, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - PLUS Plan - Owner Requests, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax County. Proposal for Implementing an Improved Planning and Land Use Control System in Fairfax County: Final Report of the Task Force on Comprehensive Planning and Land Use Control, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Fairfax County. PLUS Program. Research Paper No. 1: A Brief History of Planning, Zoning, and Environmental Controls in Fairfax County, Virginia (2 copies), 1974 January (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Fairfax County. PLUS Program. Research Paper No. 2: The Legal Basis for a Growth Control System in Fairfax County, Virginia, 1974? (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Fairfax County. PLUS Program. Papers Presented at the Countywide Public Forum, 1974 June 29 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County. Office of Comprehensive Planning. "Annotated Bibliography of PLUS Documents and Related Materials.", 1974 August 19 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax County. Letter of Robert W. Wilson, County Executive, to Lilla Richards RE: County's AAA Bond Rating, 1975 October 22 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County - Zoning Density Ranges, 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County - Thomas Grubisich article: "Fairfax Votes No on PLUS." Planning, 42:3 (April 1976), 44-46, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County Planning Commission Materials, 1973-1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Robert W. Poole, Jr. Cut Local Taxes without Reducing Essential Services. Washington, D. C.: National Taxpayers Union, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County Park Authority. "A Study of Stream Valley Erosion in Fairfax County Parks", 1978 February (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County Zoning Ordinance Summation of Recommendations RE: Density and Open Space Provisions, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County Planning Commission Mark-up of New Zoning Ordinance, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County Proffer System, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax County - Judicial Review of Local Land Use Decisions in Virginia, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority Documents, 1976-1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Audrey Moore. "The Costs of Rapid Growth.", 1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery County, Maryland. "Major State & Local Tax Burdens in Montgomery County, FY81, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County. "Fairfax Residential Growth Existing Homes Plus Planned New Homes.", 1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County. Office of Comprehensive Planning. Preserving Agriculture and Open Space in Fairfax County, and, Executive Summary: Agricultural and Forestal Districts Ordinance Report, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County. The Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia (Part 1), 1984 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County. The Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia (Part 2), 1984 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County. Office of Comprehensive Planning. Director Theodore J. Wessel. Memorandum RE: "Procedure for Reviewing Projects Subject to Title 15.1-456, Code of Virginia", 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County. "Zoning Ordinance Amendement" Studies, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County. Addendum to the Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia, 1989 March 6 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County. Policy Plan: The Countywide Policy Element of the Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia, 1990 August 6 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County. Cluster Subdivision Ordinance, 1983-1991 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Map: Fairfax County Comprehensive Land Use Plan; and Upper Potomac Planning District (map), 1995 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County. Department of Management and Budget. 1997 Demographic Estimates and Forecasts (Updates to Demographic Reports 1996.), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Map: Fairfax County. Department of Information Technology. Map: Sub Census Tracts with Supervisor Districts & Planning Districts, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County. Offices, Fairfax County, 1997 January (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County. Residential Condominium Housing Projects, 1997 January (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County. The Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia, Area II, Including Fairfax Planning District, Tysons Corner Urban Center, McLean Planning District, Vienna Planning District, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County - Plant Nurseries - Proposed Zoning Amendment, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County. Planning and Zoning Committee. "Proposed Resolution, Zoning Ordinance Amendment Group 3 Institutional and Group 6 Outdoor Recreational Special Permit Uses", 2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series 6-2: McLean Planning District Files, 1963-2002
    - Mclean Planning District - MCA Public Survey (relating to apartments, building heights, and proposed expansion of the McLean commercial center), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - McLean Planning District - Map: McLean Comprehensive Plan, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Central Park Sculpture Project, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - Economic Conditions and Potentials in the McLean Central Area (2 copies), 1970 January (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Central Business District Plan, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - Incomplete Section of a Fairfax County Planning Document for McLean Planning District Community Planning Sectors, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Central Business District Plan, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD PLUS Task Force, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Citizens Survey, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - Draft of Area II Sections (Part 1); plus cartoon from the cover of the original black binder: "People Are No Damn Good!", 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - McLean Planning District - Draft of Area II Sections (Part 2), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Central Business District - Francis L. Koenig Material, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - Projected Population for McLean CBD, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Map: Fairfax County. Land Use, Transportation and Public Facilities: Area II Plan (McLean, Vienna, & Fairfax Planning Districts), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - Controversy of McLean CBD Plan, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - Semi-Annual Plan Review, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - Plan Review Guidelines, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - New Fairfax County Zoning Code, ca. 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - Zoning Violations, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - McLean Planning District - Conditional Zoning, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - McLean Planning District - Access to Subdivisions, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - McLean Planning District - Newspaper Clippings on McLean CBD Plan, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Plan - Lilla Richards, MCA President letter RE: Weissburg Tract, 1977 December 8 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Area II Planning Documents, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Plan Testimony and Correspondence, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - Lilla Richards' Notebook on the McLean CBD Controversy (contains notes, newspaper clippings, letters, etc.), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - McLean Planning District - Materials relating to planned questions for a public hearing on the McLean CBD Plan on May 11, 1977, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - Newspaper Clippings on McLean CBD Plan, 1969-1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - "McLean Main Street", 1978? (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - Land Ownership List for the District (handwritten), ca. 1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review Task Force, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - Comparison of Population and New Homes in Region 1970-1980, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - McLean Planning District - Arlington County - Town Houses on Chain Bridge Road Newspaper Clippings and Notes, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review Task Force, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review Excerpts for Area II, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - Langley Amoco Station Issue; Langley Exxon Station Issue, 1977-1988 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review, 1976-1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Master Plan Documents, 1976, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County. Annual Plan Review Public Hearings Newspaper, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD and Dranesville District Annual Plan Review, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - McLean Planning District - Master Plan for McLean CBD, 1979-1985 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax County. Office of Comprehensive Planning. "Urban Design Handbook.", 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Study, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Concept Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Task Force Report, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Final Draft Plan (copy 1; annotated) [Note: This plan does not appear in the FCPL online catalog.], 1988 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Final Draft Plan (copy 2; annotated) [Note: This plan does not appear in the FCPL online catalog.], 1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - Ed. Abelard Letter: "Weak Leadership Dooms McLean CBD Plan?", 1988 October (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - Fairfax County Bond Referendum Information, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBD Task Force Report and Planning Commission Meeting Verbatim Excerpts, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean CBC Study, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - McLean Planning District - Preliminary Area Plan Special Development Areas: McLean Community Business Center; West Falls Church Transit Station Area, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Community Business Center (An Amendment to the Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia, 1991 Edition), 1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - McLean Planning District - Purchase of Development Rights, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - McLean Planning District - McLean Central Business Center: Open Space Design Standards (Adopted by the Board of Supervisors on April 27, 1988) 2000 edition (2 copies), 2000 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - McLean Planning District - Preliminary Staff Report 2000 Area Plans Review, 1984-2002 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - McLean Planning District - Dranesville North County Cycle 2001 Area Plans Review (APR) Task Force, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - McLean Planning District - Langley Shopping Center, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - McLean Planning District - Area Plans Review Task Force, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - McLean Planning District - The Commons Comprehensive Plan Amendment, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - McLean Planning District - Annual Plan Review, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - McLean Planning District - Dranesville District Task Force Report 2001 North County Cycle Area Plans Review, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - McLean Planning District - Areas Plan Review, Dranesville District, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Sub-series 6-3: Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1957-2002
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1957-1974; No. 1391, John O. and Mabel V. Wagner Property Rezoning, 1957-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1970-1972, C-165, Moore & Moore, 1970-1972 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971, C-310, Wallace E. and Margaret T. Johnson, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971-1972, C-282, Clinch Corporation, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971-1973, C-226, Young, Melvin T., 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971-1973, C-330, Keating (Ada's Grove), 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971-1973, C-531, Dranesville Tavern Historic District, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1971-1973, Albert, Edmund R./Solar One, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-356, Higgs/Hollinswood, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-380, Frank Luwis and James Loizou, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-396 and C-474, Moutoux (Beulah Road; 5 acres; RE-1 to RA (Agricultural), 1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-444, Cornucopia Investment, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-447, Sparger Property, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972, C-458, McLean Bank Design Standards, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972-1975, C-486 McLean Medical Building; C-491, Frederick M. Gross, 1972-1977 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972-1975, C-530, Beatty-Elmore Construction (Includes related cases 76-D-074, 76-D-108, and 76-D-113), 1972-1975 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972-1976, C-494, and 77-D-121, Weissberg Development Corporation, 1972-1978 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972-1976, C-503, Werner Krebser, 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1972-1976, C-544, Werner Krebser and C.E. Reid, Jr., 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973 C-165 - William E. and Leola J. Moore, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973 C-226, Melvin T. Young Rezoning, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-362, McCarthy Company/Elwood Estates, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-379, Norton A. Foxman/McLean Hunt Estates, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-395, Del and Elizabeth V. Ankers (Spring Hill), 1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-431, Louise Fitzgerald (including letter from Francis L. Koenig), 1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-458, McLean Bank, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-656, David M. Curtin, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, C-701, Board of Supervisors' Own Motion, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973, SP-887, Firestone Tire and Rubber Company. McLean CBD, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973-1975, C-559, Micro Systems (12 acres at Great Falls Road and Lewinsville Road, Denied), 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973-1975, C-613, Money Tract (63 acres at Rt. 7 and Springvale Road from RE-1 to C-D, Denied), 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1973-1976, C-243 Rucker Tract, 1973-1976 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974, 74-3-56, Theodore N. Lerner and H. Max Ammerman, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974, 74-3-075, Thomas M. & Marshall Gordon; warehouse, Spring Hill Road, Tysons; and 83-D-088, Rozansky & Kay, 1974-1984 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974, SP-120, Tysons Corner/Bloomingdales, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974-1976, C-703 Farley Tract (Includes Virginia Supreme Court Case, Fairfax County v. Guy O. Farley.), 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974-1976, 74-3-034, Homer E. Pinkard, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974-1977, 77-D-064 and 74-3-103, Edward E. Cousins, 1974-1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1974-1978, 74-3-137, Mortimer & Adele Lebowitz, 1974-1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1975, C-658, James L. McIlvaine, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976, 75-3-026, U. S. Home, Page Division, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976, 76-D-102, Jack Carney Parcel 25A (Lemon Road Civic Association correspondence), 1976-1983 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976-1977, 76-D-043, Ronald D. Conklin, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976-1977, 76-D-070, William H. Plank (11 acres on Balls Hill Road RE1 to R-12.5), 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976-1977, 76-D-073, John L. Hanson, Jr., 1976-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1976-1978, 76-D-091, Farley Property, McLean, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977, 77-D-007, Teno and Cecelia Roncalio, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977, 77-D-053, Glouchester Place, Peter J. Fitzgerald and Sterling W. Montague, 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)